Y'all, Kadida is taking a picture of my food.
She's one of them.
It's a lot going on.
Listen, God loves us all.
We love him.
The ones that truly want them and everything, it all going to work out.
But them that ain't right, they're going to get their due.
And they deserve it because it's wrong.
Let's stop playing.
Love everybody.
Keep playing.
Keep doing what y'all doing.
And keep loving him.
Enjoy the food, baby.
Enjoy the food.
I will.
We will.
And you realize that your suffering does not isolate you.
And that your suffering is your bridge.
That many people have suffered before you.
Many people are suffering around you.
And always will.
And all you can do is bring, hopefully, a little light into that suffering.
Enough light so the person who is suffering can begin to comprehend his suffering.
And begin to live with it.
And begin to change it.